It all ends.
The Hangover Part III is a comedy film directed by Todd Phillips.
This time, there's no wedding.
No bachelor party.
What could go wrong, right?
But when the Wolfpack hits the road, all bets are off.
Phil Wenneck, played by Bradley Cooper.
Stu Price, played by Ed Helms.
Alan Garner, played by Zach Galifianakis.
Doug Billings, played by Justin Bartha.
Mr. Chow, played by Ken Jeong.
Marshall, played by John Goodman.
The Hangover Part III is a 2013 American comedy film co-produced and
directed by Todd Phillips from a script he wrote with Craig Mazin.
It is the sequel to The Hangover Part II (2011) and the
final installment in The Hangover trilogy.
The film stars Bradley Cooper, Ed Helms, Zach Galifianakis, Ken Jeong, Justin Bartha, Mike Epps, Sasha Barrese, Gillian Vigman, Mike Vallely, Grant Holmquist, Jamie Chung,
Sondra Currie, Heather Graham, Jeffrey Tambor, and Phillips reprising their roles from the previous two installments joined by Melissa McCarthy and John Goodman.
In the film, the "Wolfpack" (Phil, Stu, Doug, and Alan) seek help for Alan after his mental breakdown,
only for things to go awry when an incident from the original film comes back to haunt them.
The Hangover Part III was announced days before the release of The Hangover
Part II and Mazin, who co-wrote Part II, was brought on board.
In January 2012, the principal actors re-signed to star.
In March 2012, Warner Bros.
announced a U.S.
Memorial Weekend release.
The supporting roles were cast between June and September 2012.
Principal photography began in September 2012 in Los Angeles, California, before moving
to Nogales, Arizona, and Las Vegas, Nevada, concluding that November.
The Hangover Part III premiered at the Westwood Village Theatre, in Los Angeles, on May
20, 2013, and was released theatrically on May 23, 2013, by Warner Bros.
The film received negative reviews from critics, who deemed
it a disappointing conclusion to the trilogy.
It also grossed $362 million worldwide against its $103 million
budget, making it the lowest-grossing film of the trilogy.
The tone is lighthearted.